<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Home on Clockwork</title><link>https://clockwork.ing/</link><description>Recent content in Home on Clockwork</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://clockwork.ing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>One System, Multiple Markets: Supporting OLX’s Path to Market-Agnostic Payments and Delivery</title><link>https://clockwork.ing/case-study/olx/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://clockwork.ing/case-study/olx/</guid><description/></item><item><title>How air up unlocked seven figure time-to-market savings by leveraging total automation</title><link>https://clockwork.ing/case-study/air-up/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://clockwork.ing/case-study/air-up/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Smash your Adapter Monolith with the Connect pattern</title><link>https://clockwork.ing/post/smash-your-adapter-monolith/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://clockwork.ing/post/smash-your-adapter-monolith/</guid><description>&lt;h3 id="tldr">TL;DR&lt;/h3>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>&amp;ldquo;Breaking down monolithic remote API Clients into individual Actions sharing a common single-function Protocol interface allows them to not only be more
decoupled at the code layer, but also simplifies both testing and extensibility.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/strong>&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Albert Latacz</title><link>https://clockwork.ing/directory/albert-latacz/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://clockwork.ing/directory/albert-latacz/</guid><description>&lt;p>Albert is a seasoned engineering lead with extensive experience in delivering high-quality software systems across various industries. He specializes in lean
and incremental development approaches, emphasizing pragmatic programming principles and value delivery without compromising on quality. Albert has a proven
track record in leading complex system migrations, re-architecting platforms, and driving process improvements. His expertise spans ERP systems, big data
solutions, and startup technology foundations, all while ensuring efficient, scalable, and secure solutions. Albert is known for his ability to balance
strategic oversight with hands-on technical leadership, fostering team collaboration, and enhancing system maintainability.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Behraam Wahid</title><link>https://clockwork.ing/directory/behraam-wahid/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://clockwork.ing/directory/behraam-wahid/</guid><description>&lt;p>Technical Program Manager with 10+ years in the fintech and retail space. I help growth stage to large companies such as Mettle, OLX and Argos deliver key projects.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>David Denton</title><link>https://clockwork.ing/directory/david-denton/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://clockwork.ing/directory/david-denton/</guid><description>&lt;p>Versatile, hands-on Engineering Lead, specialising in architecting Continually Delivered platforms (&amp;lt;15 min lead time) using heavy automation &amp;amp; shift-left methods, driving high team throughput and reductions in time-to-market. Extensive experience working on high visibility projects in a broad variety of industries, and building the teams to deliver them effectively.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Disclaimer</title><link>https://clockwork.ing/disclaimer/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://clockwork.ing/disclaimer/</guid><description>&lt;p>Last updated: 2024-05-20&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>WEBSITE DISCLAIMER&lt;/strong>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The information provided by &lt;strong>Clockwork Group&lt;/strong> (“Company”, “we”, “our”, “us”) on &lt;strong>clockwork.ing&lt;/strong> (the “Site”) is for general informational purposes only. All information on the Site is provided in good faith, however we make no representation or warranty of any kind, express or implied, regarding the accuracy, adequacy, validity, reliability, availability, or completeness of any information on the Site.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Dmitry Kandalov</title><link>https://clockwork.ing/directory/dmitry-kandalov/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://clockwork.ing/directory/dmitry-kandalov/</guid><description>&lt;p>Dmitry has been programming since DOS times. He spent over 20 years working with the JVM languages and has been writing Kotlin since 2016.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Duncan McGregor</title><link>https://clockwork.ing/directory/duncan-mcgregor/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://clockwork.ing/directory/duncan-mcgregor/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Franck Rasolo</title><link>https://clockwork.ing/directory/franck-rasolo/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://clockwork.ing/directory/franck-rasolo/</guid><description>&lt;p>I am a hands-on software architect, engineer, mentor with well over two decades of delivering reliable, repeatable, observable infrastructure and software systems to end users like clockwork using engineering discipline, eXtreme Programming practices and much software automation.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Giovanni Asproni</title><link>https://clockwork.ing/directory/giovanni-asproni/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://clockwork.ing/directory/giovanni-asproni/</guid><description>&lt;p>Experienced professional with a track record of aligning technology strategy with business goals. Expert at leading and managing cross-functional teams. Well versed in designing and implementing complex software systems. Expert in Agile Development, and in modern Software Engineering practices.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Ivan Sanchez</title><link>https://clockwork.ing/directory/ivan-sanchez/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://clockwork.ing/directory/ivan-sanchez/</guid><description>&lt;p>Technical leader with over twenty years of experience in software development and team leadership. Expert in fostering collaboration and facilitating communication between cross-functional teams and stakeholders to deliver complex software systems. Hands-on expertise in modern software architecture, design, and implementation techniques.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>James Richardson</title><link>https://clockwork.ing/directory/james-richardson/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://clockwork.ing/directory/james-richardson/</guid><description>&lt;p>James delivers reliable software products on-time, time after time.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Across many business domains and scales - James works with diverse software and product teams to take ideas
from concept to production, reliably and without drama.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Julie Camosseto</title><link>https://clockwork.ing/directory/julie-camosseto/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://clockwork.ing/directory/julie-camosseto/</guid><description>&lt;p>I help companies of all sizes optimise their processes, accelerate the delivery of innovative
technology, and drive strategic transformation. By blending management methodologies and technical
leadership, I create adaptable models that align with your organisation’s unique needs.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Privacy policy</title><link>https://clockwork.ing/privacy-policy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://clockwork.ing/privacy-policy/</guid><description>&lt;p>Effective date: 2024-05-20&lt;/p>
&lt;p>1. &lt;strong>Introduction&lt;/strong>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Welcome to &lt;strong>Clockwork Group&lt;/strong>.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>Clockwork Group&lt;/strong> (“us”, “we”, or “our”) operates &lt;strong>clockwork.ing&lt;/strong> (hereinafter referred to as &lt;strong>“Service”&lt;/strong>).&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Real World Kotlin Development</title><link>https://clockwork.ing/training/real-world-kotlin-development/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://clockwork.ing/training/real-world-kotlin-development/</guid><description>&lt;p>Would you love to take full advantage of Java without its verbosity? Wish there was a better way to avoid NullPointerExceptions? Want to be able to still rely on first-class tooling and industry support? If so then this workshop will show that is now possible.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Terms &amp; conditions</title><link>https://clockwork.ing/terms-and-conditions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://clockwork.ing/terms-and-conditions/</guid><description>&lt;p>Last updated: 2024-05-20&lt;/p>
&lt;p>1. &lt;strong>Introduction&lt;/strong>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Welcome to &lt;strong>Clockwork Group&lt;/strong> (“Company”, “we”, “our”, “us”)!&lt;/p>
&lt;p>These Terms of Service (“Terms”, “Terms of Service”) govern your use of our website located at &lt;strong>clockwork.ing&lt;/strong> (together or individually “Service”) operated by &lt;strong>Clockwork Group&lt;/strong>.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>The Ultimate Guide to IntelliJ IDEs</title><link>https://clockwork.ing/training/ultimate-guide-to-intellij-ides/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://clockwork.ing/training/ultimate-guide-to-intellij-ides/</guid><description>&lt;p>The Ultimate Guide to IntelliJ IDEs is a fast-paced, hands-on workshop that teaches developers productivity workflows. By covering the development cycle — from code browsing and editing to testing, debugging, and publishing changes to version control — you will discover new keyboard shortcuts and IDE features in each of the areas. The workshop emphasises keyboard-centric workflows, fast code navigation, and code transformations via intentions and refactorings. You will learn customisation tips, plugin recommendations, common problems, and strategies for staying focused. Whether you are new to IntelliJ IDEs or looking to refine your development flow, this workshop offers practical techniques to make the IDE work for you.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Trunk-based Development: Ship Every Commit</title><link>https://clockwork.ing/training/trunk-based-development-ship-every-commit/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://clockwork.ing/training/trunk-based-development-ship-every-commit/</guid><description>&lt;p>Ship Every Commit is an intensive, hands-on workshop that transforms how engineering teams deliver software. You&amp;rsquo;ll learn to abandon feature branches entirely and implement true trunk-based development where every commit goes directly to main and deploys to production multiple times per hour. This workshop covers the technical practices, team disciplines, and cultural shifts required to achieve continuous delivery at the commit level.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Uberto Barbini</title><link>https://clockwork.ing/directory/uberto-barbini/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://clockwork.ing/directory/uberto-barbini/</guid><description>&lt;p>Uberto is a highly experienced software engineer, Kotlin Google Developer Expert (GDE), and passionate advocate for functional programming and distributed computing. With over 20 years of experience in designing and delivering successful software products across various industries, he has a strong focus on delivering continuous business value through automation, collaborative development, and pragmatic, test-driven solutions.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>